[Music]
here's your
coffee hey man I just have to say I am a
huge fan Outcast like changed my life
thanks man so you're going to
collaborate with Andre 3000
again no how
come people grow
apart
a
greetings may I have a half C decaf mint
mocha latte fo on the bottom served in a
flower vase and if y'all got some green
food coloring back there throw it in
3,000 In the Flesh big toy is right over
there big boy I'm trying to read a
book big
boy what's up my brother from another
mother man and when I say mother you
know I'm talking about art right cuz we
got cut out of her w what's up man
what's up
Andre Andre
who I ain't going to say it man it's not
2,999 it's not
3,100 hey man what happened to you after
the show yeah
um I I must just like snuck out or
something that I thought per chance you
went
missing don't do the voices man do what
voice why why you got to do the voices
man why you doing the voices why doing
that man one green half calf half decaf
mint mocal latte foam on the bottom and
a vase I got a new idea for an album man
it's going to be just the sound of
screeching metal and then only one
spoken word per Track cool
cool n don't do that that's one of them
screeching metal sounds I talking about
earlier man half Decap mint MoCA latte
foam on the bottom and a vase or vase
you ain't he that that's your n that's
you the only niggaer that ever ordered
that drink yeah okay so what is going on
with me what is happening with me man
what the happened
man what you talking about we used to be
somebody man we used to be a team we was
on top then you went and lost your
mind can we just lose this man can we
just lose the 3,000 and just have you
talk as and tell me tell me straight up
man what
happened you know what be even better
though
man if you look into the pin wheel with
your third eye I thought you was going
to say some stupid like that and
everything will be revealed all right
man this been good man thank you thanks
for S by man as a matter of fact I got
an appointment right now to go get
fitted for a to you got to
go you leaving me that's
a
don't do it may
AOS otus and
Apollo guide you through your musical
Journey
what why does your breath smell like
biry thank you cafe Craftsman you're
welcome
sorry he he didn't actually pay for that
I got
[Music]
it